Christmas means comfort, joy and chaos.
Love the Coopers is a comedy, family, drama film directed by Jessie Nelson.
When four generations of the Cooper clan come together for their annual Christmas Eve celebration, a series of unexpected visitors and unlikely
events turn the night upside down, leading them all toward a surprising rediscovery of family bonds and the spirit of the holiday.
Charlotte Cooper, played by Diane Keaton.
Sam Cooper, played by John Goodman.
Hank Cooper, played by Ed Helms.
Ruby, played by Amanda Seyfried.
Bucky Newport, played by Alan Arkin.
Rags (voice), played by Steve Martin.
Love the Coopers (titled Christmas with the Coopers in the UK and Ireland) is a 2015 American
Christmas comedy-drama film directed by Jessie Nelson and written by Steven Rogers.
The film stars an ensemble cast, including Alan Arkin, John Goodman, Ed Helms, Diane Keaton, Jake Lacy, Anthony Mackie, Amanda
Seyfried, June Squibb, Marisa Tomei, Timothée Chalamet, Olivia Wilde and features the voice of Steve Martin.
The plot follows an imperfect family who reunites for the holidays,
as seen through the eyes of an unexpected narrator.
The film was released by CBS Films (via Lionsgate) on November 13, 2015.
It received negative reviews from critics and grossed $42.4
million against a production budget of $17 million.
The film explores themes of holiday, narration,
snowstorm, big family, family relationships.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.